What are you doing? Smelting gold?
Co robisz? Topisz złoto?
No, I'm chopping onions!
Nie, siekam cebulkę!
There is something that I want to gift you
Jest coś, co chciałbym dać ci w darze
I know it's your greatest desire, you want to become the Onioner
Wiem, że to szczyt twoich marzeń, że chcesz zostać cebularzem
I'm the best homie from the swamps, so come forth
Jestem najlepszym ziomkiem z bagien, więc podejdź
and I'll show you everything
to wszystko ci pokażę
There is something that I want to gift you
Jest coś, co chciałbym dać ci w darze
I know it's your greatest desire, you want to become the Onioner
Wiem, że to szczyt twoich marzeń, że chcesz zostać cebularzem
I'm the best homie from the swamps, so come forth
Jestem najlepszym ziomkiem z bagien, więc podejdź
and I'll show you everything
to wszystko ci pokażę
Teach me how to chop onions
Naucz mnie jak siekać cebulkę
Let me chop onions
Pozwól mi tak siekać cebulkę
Tell me how to chop onions
Powiedz mi jak siekać cebulkę
I'm chop- chop- chop- chopping onions
Sie- sie- sie- sie- siekam cebulkę.
Show me how to chop onions
Pokaż mi jak siekać cebulkę
I want to chop onions like you
Chcę jak ty tak siekać cebulkę
I want to see how to chop onions
Chcę zobaczyć jak siekać cebulkę
KHARDIMON FATAGN SCHATAR FATAGN BELIAR
KHARDIMON FATAGN SCHATAR FATAGN BELIAR
I'm chopping onions
Siekam cebulkę
Since you know my secret now,
Teraz, gdy znasz moją tajemnicę
We can chop the entire neighbourhood together
razem możemy siekać całą dzielnicę.
Chop at Thorben's
Siekać u Thorbena
Chop at Harad's
Siekać u Harada
Chop at Bosper's
Siekać u Bospera
Hagen is rather out of the question
Hagen raczej odpada
Since you know my secret now,
Teraz, gdy znasz moją tajemnicę
We can chop the entire neighbourhood together
razem możemy siekać całą dzielnicę.
Chop at Thorben's
Siekać u Thorbena
Chop at Harad's
Siekać u Harada
Chop at Bosper's
Siekać u Bospera
Hagen is rather out of the question
Hagen raczej odpada
I learned how to chop onions
Nauczyłem się jak siekać cebulkę
You let me chop onions
Pozwoliłeś mi tak siekać cebulkę
You told me how to chop onions
Powiedziałeś mi jak siekać cebulkę
I'm chop- chop- chop- chopping onions
Sie- sie- sie- sie- siekam cebulkę.
You showed me how to chop onions
Pokazałeś mi jak siekać cebulkę
I wanted to chop onions like you
Bo chciałem jak ty tak siekać cebulkę
I saw how to chop onions
Zobaczyłem jak siekać cebulkę
KHARDIMON FATAGN SCHATAR FATAGN BELIAR
KHARDIMON FATAGN SCHATAR FATAGN BELIAR
I learned how to chop onions
Nauczyłem się jak siekać cebulkę
You let me chop onions
Pozwoliłeś mi tak siekać cebulkę
You told me how to chop onions
Powiedziałeś mi jak siekać cebulkę
I'm chop- chop- chop- chopping onions
Sie- sie- sie- sie- siekam cebulkę.
You showed me how to chop onions
Pokazałeś mi jak siekać cebulkę
Because I wanted to chop onions like you
Bo chciałem jak ty tak siekać cebulkę
I saw how to chop onions
Zobaczyłem jak siekać cebulkę
KHARDIMON FATAGN SCHATAR FATAGN BELIAR
KHARDIMON FATAGN SCHATAR FATAGN BELIAR